Gabriela Polanco-Ferreyra

Contact

gabrielapolancoferreyra@gmail.com +16466374077

www.gabrielapolancoferreyra.com linkedin.com/in/gabriela-polanco-ferreyra

Skills

Design thinking
User research
UX design
UI design
Wireframing
Prototyping
Problem solving
Criticial thinking
Resolution and management of conflicts
Figma
Adobe creative suite
HTML & CSS
VS code

Education

UX/UI

Ironhack Lisbon Jan 2022- March 2022

Web development

Ironhack Remote
October 2020-December 2020

Attorney

University of Buenos Aires, Argentina. 2011-2018

Languages

Spanish (native) English (Full professional proficiency) French (Elementary proficiency)

About

My first professional steps were in the world of law until I decided to travel and learn about other realities and cultures.

The possibility of creating worlds, products, and experiences has become my passion lately. After studying web development, I understood that designing interfaces and users experience challenges me. I'm driven by the desire to make this world more accessible, fair, and democratic.

Experience

Web Designer-Freelancer | Jan 2021 - Present

- Implemented organizational, problem-solving, and innovative skills and helped to transform people's ideas into appealing designs.
- •Communicated design ideas using user flows, process flows, site maps, and wireframes.
- •Prototype wireframes using Figma.

Content Analyst-UENI (UK) Remote 2019-2020

- Worked with the operations team while creating websites for SMEs business located in various parts of the world
- Developed and edited the content for the client's website.
- Created the SEO for the client business to be top on Google.
- Partnered with management to create, develop and implement quality initiatives, resulting in better outputs.

Legal Administrative Assistant - Federal Department of Justice, Argentina | 2013 - 2018

- •Researched laws, court decisions, and other documents relevant to cases before court to aid in judge's decision-making.
- •Facilitated legal team by conducting research, drafting briefs, gathering information, and interpreting legal documents.
- •Created and prepared legal drafts by organizing and assembling information for legal documents and forms, including declarations, discovery requests, and complaints.